One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Inherited will...
the tides of time,
and humanity's dreams...
They cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
Now tell me...
where Crocodile is!
Rainbase, the City of Dreams
Luffy-san is absolutely right.
I've made up my mind now.
Let's head to Crocodile's location!
Yeah!
That certainly seems to be
the quickest route.
Meaning no more of this annoying,
roundabout traveling.
So, where is this damn Crocodile?
Let's see here...
This is Alubarna, the capital city
where my father rules.
And the Rebel Army is currently here,
preparing to invade Alubarna.
So we need to take care of Crocodile
before that can happen.
Crocodile is here. Rainbase.
Rainbase...
It's about a day's walk north of here.
C'mon,
I told you two to quit moaning!
You get to ride the camel,
so you can't complain!
Yeah! Let us ride, too!
You camel-woman!
Nami-mel!
Good one!
Chopper! You haven't
collapsed today!
Yeah. I'm gonna try extra hard.
Vivi. Does Rainbase have water?
Yes, there's no problem there.
It's a gambling town,
detached from the Rebellion.
Ooh! Gambling?!
Hey, now! What're you thinking?!
I guess there are carefree cities
even here in Arabasta.
Gum-Gum No Way!
No! No! No!
Gimme some!
Gum-Gum No Way!
C'mon! Just a sip!
This is why we have it!
That dry old guy spent all night
digging this water up!
We can't just drink it like
it's nothing, you dumbhead!
Wow! There are times you
can restrain yourself!
Of course I can! How rude!
You're rude!
Can't take another step... W-Water...
So?! How long until Rainbase?!
Luffy-san.
Thanks. I never could have
made this decision on my own.
Then gimme food.
Huh?
After I kick Crocodile's ass,
gimme food till I burst!
Okay! I promise!
Rebel Army Camp in Katorea
Kappa
Nanohana Shoeshine Boy
Please, Koza! Let me join
the Rebel Army!
Not a chance.
Why not?! I have the right
to join the Rebellion too, don't I?!
I despise the king!
Let me fight with you!
Show him, Farafla.
He got this protecting me
in the middle of a battle.
Wanna see the medical tents
and graves, too?
Th-That doesn't scare me!
Towns dried up, and many people
died 'cause the king stole the rain!
And I got lotsa friends
who got sick from it!
It's all the king's fault!
I wanna fight too!
I'm not afraid of getting
hurt or even dying!
Then leave. Our opinions
are too different.
We're all afraid,
and none of us want to fight.
Then why do you fight?!
It's not that we want to.
We have to.
This country needs us to.
Whether you get it or not,
it's got nothing to do with you.
Leave.
I told you to leave, dammit!
This is no place for kids!
What's wrong, Koza?
It's not like you to lose your temper at children.
It was like looking
at my old self. It really got to me.
I haven't changed at all...
Do we have enough weapons?
No. It's proving difficult...
Spread the word to the other towns.
As soon as we're armed and ready,
we launch an all out
assault on Alubarna!
Alubarna Palace
Sire! It's only a matter of time until
the Rebel Army attacks Alubarna!
We must take action
before it's too late!
Silence! I told you no!
This is not a children's quarrel!
Is retaliation what you want?!
But, Your Majesty, at this rate,
the country will be in mortal danger!
And what of it?
It's been clear since
the dance powder incident
that someone is trying
to destroy our country!
You want to
destroy our countrymen
without knowing who's
pulling the strings?
That would be
the destruction of this country.
Listen! A country is its people!
However, the mastermind has
not yet revealed who they are.
This shadow will devour our country,
and then it will be too late!
No. Please understand.
The king won't allow us
to take the offensive.
We can barely even appease
the soldiers at this point.
If only Igaram-san were here
at a time like this...
Igaram says he's leaving
the country for a while?
Lt. Chaka "the Jackal"
(Acting Commander)
Arabasta Royal Guard
Lt. Pell "the Falcon"
As we speak, he and Princess Vivi
are probably still hard at work,
trying to figure out who's behind this.
I wonder where they are.
Sir Chaka! Sir Pell!
What is it?!
Karoo has returned!
He has?!
Sire! Who is that letter from?!
It's Vivi's handwriting,
without a doubt...
Sire! Does that mean–
Karoo delivered a letter from Vivi?!
Father. Everything written here
is true. It is fact.
The person trying to bring suffering
and ruin to this kingdom
is none other than Crocodile!
Igaram is yet another who has fallen
at the hands of Crocodile.
Crocodile! I stupidly believed
he worked for the government!
I never would have imagined he was
trying to usurp the throne!
Igaram-san...
He gave his life for Princess Vivi
and this land...
And now, there are powerful people
lending me their strength.
If I continue with them, we can
make a difference in this kingdom.
The light of hope is here!
Arabasta will be saved!
Please have faith, Father!
Vivi.
It says you fought valiantly,
too, Karoo. You've done well.
You were injured? Let me see.
Anyway, no matter what happens,
our left arms prove
we're definitely crewmates!
Chaka.
We know now who our enemy is!
Prepare the soldiers to march!
Neither Vivi's resolve
nor Igaram's death will be in vain!
We act immediately!
We're heading to
Crocodile's home, Rainbase!
Please wait, sire! Rainbase is too far
away for anything to be "immediate"!
Crocodile presently has
the support of the populace.
With all due respect,
even more so than you.
If we attack Rainbase,
the Rebel Army will use
that as a chance to storm the palace!
If that happens–
And so what if the Rebel Army
were to take the palace?!
I've told you before!
A country is its people!
Even if the Royal Army falls,
as long as Crocodile is defeated,
the citizens will rebuild their country!
But, consider if we clash
with the Rebel Army instead!
Crocodile will assuredly
have the last laugh!
Sire...
You're that dedicated to–
Even if by some chance
the Rebel Army doesn't stop,
we need only take out Crocodile!
We're up against one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Crocodile is not weak willed.
This battle will not be
without sacrifices before its end.
Chaka! I'm holding a war meeting!
Assemble the officers!
Pell! Go on ahead and
conduct reconnaissance!
Yes, sire!
It seems we've been severely
underestimating His Majesty.
What powerful spirit!
We go to battle tomorrow morning!
Yes, sire!
Deploy all soldiers to Rainbase!
I see it...
Is that it?
Rainbase?
Oh! Did we make it?!
Crocodile!
Alright! Time to beat up Crocodile!
So this is Rainbase!
By the way, does Baroque Works
know we're in this country now?
Most likely.
We ran into Mr. 2, so we
should assume they know we're here.
So what?!
They know what we look like!
We can't do much of anything
while we're in Rainbase!
Why not?!
If we get spotted first,
Crocodile can use just about
any method to take us out.
Assassination
is their area of specialty.
Come out, Crocodile!
Were you even listening?!
In any case, no matter
who we run into,
I'll protect Nami-san and Vivi-chan !
You two girls can call me "Prince"!
Prince.
Don't make me kick your ass!
– Prince... Water...
– Water...
Shut up, you guys!
Water! Need water!
Me too!
Water! Water!
Wait! Luffy!
Take money with you!
Rainbase, the City of Dreams
Captain Smoker.
Why do you think the Straw Hats
will show up here in Rainbase?
Dunno. Call it intuition.
Alright!
We can get water here, Usopp!
Water!
Plus, something stinks
about this country.
I've got a hunch something big
is lurking in the shadows.
Old lady! Water!
A barrel of water! No, five!
Five barrels of water!
Do you think there really
is a connection
between the Baroque Works
criminal organization and Straw Hat?
Here!
All I know is that Straw Hat
is out to get Crocodile,
one of the Seven Warlords.
This water's great, you jerk!
It's great, you bastard!
Let's hurry and take some
to the others!
I need to take a leak.
Can we really count on them?
They can do little errands
just fine. Don't worry.
I dunno. I bet they'll come back
with a buncha trouble again.
I'd do warm-up exercises
if I were you.
Run!
Yeah!
Got that barrel?!
Damn it! We're going after 'em,
Tashigi! Gather the marines!
Yes, sir!
Um, how much do I owe you?
If you know those kids, you better
pay for the water they took, too!
Y-Yes! I'm sorry for the trouble!
Why is the Navy here?!
How should I know?! Just run!
The Navy's chasing 'em again!
No way!
So why are they running this way?!
Hey! Tony-kun hasn't come back yet!
Don't worry! He'll manage!
Hey, guys! The Navy's here!
You're the one bringing them here!
Catch 'em for sure this time!
They're quick to run away,
I'll give 'em that!
This isn't a good idea!
Baroque Works is gonna spot us...
if we run through the city!
I think it's too late for that.
Then it's decided! Let's go!
Huh?!
To where Crocodile is!
Right, Vivi?!
Yes! Do you see that
alligator-roofed building up ahead?!
That's Crocodile's casino:
Rain Dinners!
There, huh?! So that's
where Crocodile is?!
It'd be best if we split up!
It looks that way!
Alright! See you later!
Yeah!
Let's meet at the gator house!
They split up!
Don't let 'em escape!
Come and get me, Smokey!
You got real guts!
Don't think you can
keep running forever!
White Vine!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
That was close!
Damn!
Whoops!
Mr. Bushido! This direction, too!
It's them! No doubt about it!
Kill 'em!
The Baroque Works millions!
A tiger at the front gate
and a wolf at the back, huh?
Go on without me!
Hurry!
R-Right!
Usopp!
Look after Nami-san !
What?!
I'll hold 'em off!
You can count on me!
Sanji-kun...
We are!
Without that smoke freak around,
they're nothing to worry about.
My deepest condolences.
I hope Mr. Bushido will be all right!
Is that all you got?
Try again some other time.
Roronoa Zoro! We meet again!
That voice...
I've been looking
for you a long time!
Where do you get off
cutting down regular citizens?!
There's more going on here than it seems!
Besides, I have no
desire to fight you!
We settled our match in Loguetown!
No, we didn't!
I haven't even landed
a single blow yet!
She looks like her!
Way too much like her!
And quit it with that face, will ya?!
C-Come again?! You're still
trying to ridicule me?!
You will pay for this!
Dammit! She's the one person
I can't deal with!
Wait!
Bastards! Get back here!
No!
It's definitely them!
W-We did it!
Way to go, Usopp!
Look! Up ahead!
The entrance to Rain Dinners!
It's in the middle of a lake!
Is no one here yet?!
Alright! Let's blast 'em!
Start with those two!
The enemy?!
Zoro!
Wasn't Vivi with you?!
Yeah! Is she not here yet?!
She might've gone inside!
Let's hurry, then!
Luffy!
Get back here!
Smoke-Smoke's there!
Hey! Let's go! Run inside, guys!
We're going in?
He's in there,
isn't he?!
Oh? Vivi and the pirates
are here in town?
Yes. We just received word
from the millions.
Go welcome the foolish rats.
Yes, sir.
Listen, Crocodile!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
I'm coming for you!